https://janarps.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
SHOPFAQMEDIAInstructional VideosBlog VideosWebinarsPodcastsBLOGCONTACT
Search for:
SHOPCartFAQMEDIAInstructional VideosBlog VideosWebinarsPodcastsBLOGABOUTCONTACT
Privacy PolicyJenny Ly2018-01-07T07:50:41+00:00
This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) covers Jan Arps’ Traders’ Toolbox treatment of information that you provide to us or that we collect from you when you are visiting the Website and when you use our products and services. This Privacy Policy should be read in connection with our Website Terms and Conditions.
This Privacy Policy applies only to information you provide to us online or that we collect from you while visiting or using our Website. It does not apply to information we have obtained offline or through other means.
Jan Arps’ Traders’ Toolbox reserves the right to use and control the information collected on the Website. We will not share this information with any third party, other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
When you subscribe to a product or service, we request the appropriate billing information on our order form. This information includes your credit card number, expiration date and billing address (“Order Information”). Order Information is kept with your Registration Information in a database and will be retained for future purchases. We do not rent or sell your name or other personal information.
If you want to send an inquiry email using the website, your name, address, email address and phone may be collected. This information is kept in an inquiry database.
